<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Task2s on ICASSP 2024: Auditory EEG challenge</title>
    <link>https://exporl.github.io/auditory-eeg-challenge-2024/task2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Task2s on ICASSP 2024: Auditory EEG challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://exporl.github.io/auditory-eeg-challenge-2024/task2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>leaderboard</title>
      <link>https://exporl.github.io/auditory-eeg-challenge-2024/task2/leaderboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exporl.github.io/auditory-eeg-challenge-2024/task2/leaderboard/</guid>
      <description> All results Group nameSubmission number Within subjects mean Within subjects std Heldout subjects mean Heldout subjects std total score </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task 2: Regression</title>
      <link>https://exporl.github.io/auditory-eeg-challenge-2024/task2/description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exporl.github.io/auditory-eeg-challenge-2024/task2/description/</guid>
      <description>Schematic overview of the regression task Description Task 2 is a regression problem: To reconstruct the mel spectrogram from the EEG. Compared to the challenge from last year, this objective is slightly more difficult, as it contains more speech information than the envelope. We define a mel spectorgram with 10 subbands, distributed between 0 and 5000 Hz, calculated by the librosa library ( see preprocessing_code/mel.py). After reconstruction, a metric to measure the similarity is used between the reconstructed mel and the original mel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Set Task 2</title>
      <link>https://exporl.github.io/auditory-eeg-challenge-2024/task2/test_set/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://exporl.github.io/auditory-eeg-challenge-2024/task2/test_set/</guid>
      <description>Provided test dataset The test data for this task can be downloaded from here. The password is the same one as provided for the training set. The directory contains following items:
sub-x_mapping.json: These files link the EEG files to the possible stimuli. Since you are free to use whatever version of the data you want, these json files contain keys to the EEG files. Each entry in the json file is of the form: (segment_ID) : {&amp;rsquo;eeg&amp;rsquo;: eeg_id}.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
